(綱手)うん… では暁を
うかがわせる動きは➡
Then there were no developments
that would suggest
the Akatsuki organization.
存在しないと。
(アスマ)ええ。
That's right...
However, there is probably
no doubting
(アスマ)ですが 深刻な事態に
なることは間違いないでしょう。
that a serious situation will develop.
It was a horrible sight...
それは無惨なありさまでした。
(アスマ)一夜にして村が襲撃され➡
The village was attacked
in one night
and most of the villagers were dead.
多くの村人が亡くなっていました。
((雨隠れ…))
Hidden Rain...
その後 やはり国境線を
縫うように いくつかの村が…➡
And sure enough, as if weaving
along the border,
several other villages
were attacked after that.
They were all Land of Fire villages.
すべて 火ノ国の村です。
Asuma, don't rush to conclusions.
(綱手)アスマ 結論を急ぐな。
I understand that.
心得てますよ。
わざわざ雨隠れの印を残していく。
They go to the trouble of leaving
the Hidden Rain mark...
そのやり方も気にくわねえ！
I don't care for that approach at all!
Is there someone
who wants to start a war?
戦争を
仕掛けたがっているヤツがいる。
Perhaps... But sometimes
a guess hits the mark exactly.
とも言えます… が そのもの
ズバリということもあります。
Is there no information on developments
with the Hidden Rain?
雨隠れの動きで
何か情報はありませんか？
Nothing at this point.
今のところは何も。
But what we should be
concerned with is...
(アスマ)しかし懸念すべきは…。
(綱手)火ノ国か？
The Land of Fire, huh...?
Yes... The Feudal Lord...
ええ。 大名に…。
There might be someone
血気はやって大名を
あおるものがでるやもしれんか。
who recklessly instigates
the Feudal Lord, huh?
かつての守護忍十二士のように…。
Like with the Guardian
Shinobi Twelve before.
(綱手)武闘派のダンゾウに➡
The ammunition to intrude
in the situation
might be supplied to Danzo,
the old military faction leader.
しゃしゃり
出てくる材料を与えかねんな…。
一癖も二癖もある方ですからね…。
He's a sly customer to deal with,
after all.
Assign some Anbu members
and village Jonin
暗部 ならびに里の上忍を割き➡
and have them try to find some
information around the area of the border.
国境付近の情報を探らせる。
But since we don't know
the present situation,
…が 現状がわからぬ今
極秘に行動させる。
have them work in secrecy.
決して我が里から
アクションを起こさぬよう心得させよ。
And make sure they know
that our village is absolutely
not to stir up any action.
大名には
私から書簡を送っておこう。
I will send a letter
to the Feudal Lord.
Yes, ma'am.
(シズネ)はい！
アスマ班は➡
Team Asuma will move out
the moment there are
any new developments.
新たな動きが
入り次第動いてもらう。
Stand by until then.
それまでは待機！
わかりました。 では…。
Understood.
I will be leaving then...
Excuse me.
(ヤマト)失礼します。
The Guardian Shinobi Twelve...
守護忍十二士…。
Come to think of it,
Asuma was once...
そういえば かつてアスマさんも…。
Yeah. In those days when
he was a kid around twenty,
あぁ
ハタチかそこらのガキの時分には➡
火ノ国のため
なすべきことをなす！
he spewed some kind of
tongue-twister rationalization like...
"I'll do what I have to do
for the Land of Fire..."
なんて 舌を噛みそうな
理屈を さんざんぱら叩いて➡
jumps down the Third Hokage's throat,
and leaves the village.
三代目に噛みつき里を出て行った。
Well, from my standpoint,
it was just a simple father-son argument.
ま 私から見たら単なる親子ゲンカだ。
Uh-huh...
It happened ten years ago.
(綱手)それが10年前…
守護忍十二士の一部が➡
One part of the Guardian Shinobi Twelve
staged an unsuccessful coup
in order to turn the Land of Fire
into a military superpower.
火ノ国を軍事大国とすべく
クーデター未遂事件を起こした。
守護忍十二士は まっ二つに割れ➡
The Guardian Shinobi Twelve
were split right in two,
and Asuma and his comrades
brought that group down.
アスマと仲間たちは
その一派を壊滅させたのさ。
(ナルト)オッス アスマ先生！
Hi, Asuma-sensei!
Oh, Naruto. Are you making progress
with your training?
(アスマ)おう ナルト 修業進んだか？
Well, I actually
didn't have time for that.
いや それどころじゃ
なかったってばよ。
I see...
What're you doing here?
そうか。
何やってんだ？ こんなところで。
ヤマト隊長が
声かけるまで待ってろって。
Captain Yamato told us to
wait out here until he calls us.
Hey! What're you doing glaring
like that?!
(サクラ)ちょっと
何ガンたれてんのよ！
Well, I...
(ソラ)いや オレは…。
すみません もう 目つき悪くて。
I'm sorry he has such
mean-looking eyes...
Hey, you apologize, too!
ほら アンタも謝る！
Wh-Why do I have to...?
何で オレが…。
So that's what happened?
そんなことが あったんですか…。
And although they lost their lives,
(ヤマト)そのとき
命を落としながらも➡
クーデター一派を食い止めた
キタネ ナウマ トウウ セイト。
Kitane, Nauma, Tou'u and Seito
stopped the coup.
盗まれた ご遺骸は
彼らだったのです。
It was their bodies that were stolen.
What did you say?!
なんだって!?
I am very sorry.
There were four thieves...
申し訳ありません。 賊は４名。
and they were a group that used
quite advanced Earth Style Jutsu.
かなり高度な
土遁を駆使する輩たちでしたが…。
What are they intending to
use the bodies for?
賊は ご遺骸を
どうする気なんでしょう？
Things will become problematic
万一 彼らの中に眠る
貴重な術の情報が➡
should the precious Jutsu information
resting with them spread to other lands.
他国などに流れれば
やっかいなことになります。
う～ん…。
Yes...
Also, Sai was injured during the mission
and I had no choice
(ヤマト)それと 任務中 サイが負傷し➡
短期間ではありますが
離脱せざるをえなくなりました。
but to have him leave the team,
though it will only be for a short time.
And as for his replacement
on Team Kakashi,
そのかわりといっては なんですが
ともに任務に当たった➡
I would like to add
the young novice monk
火ノ寺の見習い僧の少年を
カカシ班に入れたいのですが…。
who was also
assigned to the mission.
But, well...
その…。
どうした？
What is it?
はぁ…。
Well...
Once I fly,
habataitara
I won't be coming back, I said.
modorena ito itte
And I set out.
mezashita no wa
For that blue, blue sky.
aoi aoi ano sora
I haven't learned "sadness" yet.
kanashimi wa mada oboerarezu
And I'm just starting to grasp "misery".
setsunasa wa ima tsukami hajimeta
Even this feeling I hold towards you.
anata e to idaku kono kanjou mo
Is now turning into "words".
ima kotoba ni wakatteku
Waking up from the dream of this unknown world.
michi naru sekai no yume kara mezamete
I spread these wings and fly.
kono hane wo hiroge tobi datsu
Once I fly,
habataitara
I won't be coming back, I said.
modorena ito itte
And I set out.
mezashita no wa
For that blue, blue sky.
aoi aoi ano sora
Knowing I'll find the answer,
tsuki nuketara
If I pierce through it.
mitsukaru to shitte
if I break free,
furikiru hodo
From that blue, blue sky.
aoi aoi ano sora
Teammate
I see...
(綱手)なるほどな。
So those four grave robbers were
lying in wait for each of you?
(綱手)では
その４人の墓荒らしどもは➡
お前たちの いずれかを
待ち伏せていたと…。
At that point in time,
(ヤマト)あの時点で いちばん
狙われる可能性が高かった➡
I had Chiriku, the one they were
most likely targeting, leave the unit.
地陸さんには 隊から
離脱してもらったので➡
So I think we can eliminate him.
除外できるかと…
となると 暁同様 人柱力…。
In which case...
there's a slight chance that,
like the Akatsuki organization,
ナルトを狙ったという可能性も
ゼロではありませんが➡
they were targeting Naruto
who is a Jinchuriki.
我々が 火ノ寺へ派遣されたことは
たまたまですし…。
But it was a coincidence
that we were dispatched
to the Fire Temple.
(綱手)で 残るは その ソラ
という子というわけか…。
And so, that leaves that kid
called Sora, huh?
Yes. In which case,
I think it would be in our best interests
えぇ その場合 わが里において
行動をともにしたほうが➡
to have him in the village
working with us.
得策ではないかと。 もちろん
火ノ寺とも相談のうえです。
Of course, this is after consultation
with the Fire Temple.
Anyway, we're counting on you, Sora!
とにかく お願いよ！ ソラ。
綱手様の前では行儀よくしててね。
Behave yourself in front
of Tsunade-sama, okay?!
(サクラ)じゃないと
恐ろしいことになるんだから！
If you don't...
something terrible will happen.
そうだぞ 綱手のばあちゃんだけは
シャレきかねえんだからな！
That's right.
Witty remarks don't work
on Grandma Tsunade!
Huh? Is that
supposed to scare me?
あぁ？ んなことで
オレが びびるかよ！
火影だか ばあさんだか
知んねえけどよ➡
I don't know if she's an old lady
or a Hokage or what.
But I'll pay my respects!
オレが拝んでやるぜ。
Naruto! Sakura! Bring Sora-kun in!
(ヤマト)ナルト サクラ！
ソラ君を連れてきて。
Y-Yes, sir.
(サクラ)は… はい！ ほら 来て！
- Okay, come on!
- Whoa...
See you later, Asuma-sensei.
(サクラ)それじゃ アスマ先生！
(ソラ)おい！
H-Hey?!
Hurry up!
(サクラ)早く！ 失礼します！
Excuse us.
(サクラ)綱手様!!
Tsunade-sama!
Hurry up and apologize!
早く謝れ！
There are great limits
to my patience!
仏の面は 一度っきりなんだよ！
Who's an old lady?!
誰が ばあさんだって!?
I called you a Buddhist saint!
菩薩さんって言いました！
A Buddhist saint?!
(綱手)菩薩？
Yes, yes!
かわいいこと言ってくれるねぇ。
この小坊主ちゃん。 合格！
Well, doesn't this little boy
say adorable things?
You pass!
(綱手)ようこそ 木ノ葉の里へ。
(ソラ)ちょっ… ちょっと！
Welcome to the Hidden Leaf Village.
H-Hey. That hurts...
《大きくなったな ソラ…》
You've sure grown up, Sora.
Okay, I have to write up a report,
so I'm off.
(ヤマト)じゃあ ボクは 報告書
作らないといけないから これで。
I'll take Sai to the hospital.
(サクラ)私も サイを
病院に連れていくわ。
Okay...
(サイ)はい。
えっ… あっ…。
Hey, wait a minute.
I need to continue with my training!
ちょっと待つってばよ！
オレも修業の続きを…。
Training, my foot. Kurenai-sensei's
out on a mission, right?
なにが修業よ。 カカシ先生は
任務に出て留守じゃない。
You show Sora
around the village.
(サクラ)アンタは ソラに
里を案内してあげて。
Sora's now our teammate
on Team Kakashi.
(サクラ)ソラは もう
カカシ班のチームメイトなんだからね。
Hell no! Why do I have to be
with this obnoxious guy?!
冗談じゃねえってばよ！ なんで
こんな危ねえヤツなんかと…。
オレだって こんな
罰当たり野郎と一緒なんて…！
I don't want to be with
this awful jerk, either.
Yeah, yeah.
(サクラ)はい はい！
そうやって二人で➡
You guys just go at it
as much as you like.
好きなだけ やってなさい。
もう のらないから。
I won't be joining in anymore.
Let's go, Sai.
(サクラ)行きましょ サイ。
(サイ)はい…。
Right...
Okay Naruto,
I'll leave Sora to you.
(ヤマト)じゃあ ナルト。 ソラを頼んだよ。
Y-You guys are dirty!
汚ねえぞ みんな！
(ソラ)はっ… ヤツらも同じか。
So they're the same, huh?
Huh?
I'm just a burden, aren't I?
結局 オレが やっかいなんだろう。
おい それ 違うぞ。
Hey, it's not like that.
サクラちゃんも ヤマト隊長も
やっかい者なんて思ってねえ。
Sakura-chan and Captain Yamato
don't think you're a burden.
思ってたらな お前を 里へなんか
連れてきやしねえだろ！
If they did,
you wouldn't have been brought here
to this village, right?!
…わかってるよ。
I know that.
Then what is it?!
だったら…
お前 復讐なんて やめろよ。
Forget... about your revenge.
それとこれとは関係ねえだろ！
そうだけどよ…。
The two things aren't related!
I know, but...
My dad was a hero to me.
(ソラ)父さんは
オレにとって ヒーローだった。
心が強く たくましい人だった。
He was a courageous man with
a powerful inner strength.
(ソラ)５歳までの記憶しか
ねえけどな。
I only have memories of him
up until I was five.
The people at the Fire Temple
never told me anything.
火ノ寺のヤツらは
なんにも教えてくれなかった。
And yet, I happened to hear
about my dad being killed...
それでも 父さんが殺されたことは
オレの耳にも入った。
as they shouted in contempt...
さげすむように 吐き捨てて…。
"He got what he deserved!"
"Killing him was the right thing!"
(ソラ)自業自得だ
殺されて当然のことをした って！
My dad could never have
done anything devious!
(ソラ)父さんが
曲がったことをするはずねえ！
It must be some kind of mistake!
絶対 なんかの間違いだ!!
オレは ソイツを正す。 そして
そのうえで父さんを殺したヤツを…。
I'll rectify that...
And then after I've done that,
I'll get the guy who killed my dad!
You...
お前…。
So don't be following
me everywhere.
(ソラ)だから オレに
まとわりつくんじゃねえよ！
It's irritating!
うっとうしいぜ。
うっとうしいって…。
Irritating?
I'm showing concern for you
and that's your attitude?
心配すりゃ その態度か！
Huh? That's just called meddling!
フン！ それが
おせっかいってんだよ。
I'll feel out the enemy
on my own.
敵情視察は１人でやるぜ。
I'll take over this village...
in ten minutes!
こんな里
10分で しめてやっからよ。
Just do whatever you want!
お前は もう！
ったく… 勝手にしろ!!
I don't want to deal with you, either!
オレだってな お前の相手なんか
したかねえっつうの！ フン!!
What's he going to take over?
何をしめるっていうんだ？ アイツ…。
For crying out loud, where'd he go?
ったく… どこ
行っちまったんだってばよ？
えっ!?
You want to fight, huh?!
やんのか!? コラ！
I won't go easy on you just
because you're a dog, you awful jerk.
犬だからって容赦しねえぞ
このバチ当たりヤロウ！
(赤丸)ワン ワン！
赤丸に メンチかよ…。
He's glaring at Akamaru?
This is not good.
If Kiba shows up here...
まずいってばよ。
こんなとこに キバが現れたら…。
Oh, Naruto.
(キバ)おう！ ナルトじゃねえか。
帰ってたのか。
You're back?
Oh, Akamaru! There you are.
(キバ)おっ！ 赤丸。
こんな所にいたのか。
Who's he?
I haven't seen him before.
なんだ？ アイツ。 知らねえ顔だな。
Oh... he's...
あぁ… そのアイツは… あっ！
Hey, you! What're you trying
to do to Akamaru, huh?!
(キバ)おい テメエ！
赤丸に何しようってんだ？ あぁ!?
You're the owner?
テメエが飼い主か？
If you are,
then keep a leash on him
飼い主だったら
ちゃんと ヒモつけて➡
and train him not to bark
all of a sudden!
いきなり吠えねえように
しつけとけ！
Akamaru isn't a pet!
赤丸は ペットじゃねえ！ テメエが
怪しいから 赤丸が吠えたんだよ。
And he barked at you
because you're suspicious!
Where are you from?!
どこのもんだ!?
(赤丸)ワン ワン！
I'm from the Fire Temple.
火ノ寺のもんよ。
木ノ葉の里をしめにきたんだよ！
I've come to take over this village.
Huh?
はぁ？
ワンワン！
Sorry about this, Kiba.
I can explain.
いや～ わりいな キバ！
He's kind of with our team and...
コイツ ちょっと 訳あって
オレたちの班でさ…。
Naruto! Is he with you?
ナルト お前の連れか？
(ソラ)ふざけんな！
Knock it off! I'm not friends
or anything with this guy!
こんなヤツ ダチでもなんでもねえよ！
いいから お前は黙ってろ ソラ！
Just keep quiet, Sora!
Fighting's no good, you guys.
(チョウジ)ケンカはよくないな。 みんなさ
カリカリしないで 仲よく…。
Don't be so testy and let's get along.
Shut up, Fatty!
(ソラ)うっせぇ デブ！
D-Did you just say...
(チョウジ)い… 今 デブって言った…？
"Fatty"?
Yeah. So what of it?!
あぁ!? それが どうした？
Th-This is not good...
(シカマル)ま… まずいぞ…。
しまった…。
Uh oh...
All right! Let's have a battle royale!
(ソラ）よっしゃ！ バトルロイヤルだ!!
Hey, are you an idiot?!
って… バカか！
相手は テメエ１人だっつうの!!
You're the only opposition here!
Let's go, Choji!
(キバ)いくぞ チョウジ！
ヘッ！ そんなデブと 何ができる!?
Heh! What can you do
with a Fatty like that?!
You said, "fatty" again, eh?!
また デブって言ったな…。
I'm not fat! I'm a chubby-type!
ボクはデブじゃない！ ポッチャリ系だ!!
わっ！ バカ やめろ!!
Whoa, you idiot! Cut it out!
All right! Keep a hold on him, Choji!
(キバ)よし！
そのまま捕まえてろ チョウジ!!
(ソラ)くっ！ きたねぇぞ オメエら!!
You guys are dirty!
Oh...! It's one against everyone?
あっ！ １人と全員かよ。
しゃあねえだろ。
It can't be helped. He asked for it.
ヤツがまいた種だぜ。
いや でも だからってよ…。
Uh, even so...
Ohh, I guess I have no choice!
ああっ しようがねえ！
Hey! Enough, already!
おい！ もう やめろって！
ナルト…！
Naruto! Are you taking his side?
コイツに味方しようってのかよ！
違うってばよ！
No, I'm not!
But I can't just sit here
and do nothing.
でも 黙って見てるわけにも
いかねえからな！
Huh? Why side with an outsider?!
(キバ)あん？ なんで よそ者に！
I have no choice.
よそ者じゃねえんだよ コイツは！
He's a Team Kakashi comrade, so...
カカシ班の仲間だからな！
仲間…。
Comrade...
So let's just calm down now and...
だから ここは
落ち着いて 話し合い…。
And let's discuss this...
Hey! You're hitting me
with your punches!
ソラ！ お前のパンチが
当たってんだよ！
You're the one who's been
hitting me with your kicks!
テメエの蹴りこそ さっきから…！
What?!
なにを…！
《バカか コイツら…》
Are these guys morons...?
That hurts! Hey!
イテエな こら…！
You'll never get me to join in.
お前も加われなんて
言いっこなしっすよ。
Hah... That wouldn't suit you, right?
フッ… お前は
そんな ガラじゃないだろ。
It's enough to just
let them fight it out.
あんなのは ヤツらだけで十分だ。
Now we've got one more person
in this village, huh?
この里には もう１人いますね。
ん…？
(リー)ぬおお～っ！
Why wasn't I invited to
(リー)夕やけ空で
男の友情を育む拳会議に➡
the "meeting of fists under a sunset sky
to develop the friendship of men?!"
なんで… ボクを
呼んでくれなかったんですか!?
They can fight forever
because they're tough.
(シカマル)ヤツら タフだから
いつまでも戦ってますよ。
Well, I guess
that's about enough.
ま そろそろかな。
えっ…？
Huh?!
獣人分身！
Man Beast Clone!
Leaf...
木ノ葉！
倍化の術！
Expansion Jutsu!
Shadow Clone...!
影分身！
風遁！
Wind Style!
Uzumaki Barrage!
Beast Wave Palm!
Severe Hurricane!
Human Boulder!
Fang Over Fang!
(キバ)牙通牙…！
What's this?!
これは…！
ヘッ…！
(チョウジ)デブじゃな～い！
- I'm not fat!
- Oh!
Whoa.
(シカマル)うわ～っ！
Hey!
(アスマ)こらっ！
さてと 拳会議が終わったら
焼き肉で打ち上げだ！
Now then, let's have a party
at the Barbe-Q
after the "meeting of fists".
Barbe-Q!
(チョウジ)焼き肉！
(リー)いいですね！
That sounds good!
A dinner with tons of guys!
(リー)男だらけの食事会…！
So after all's said and done
it's another party, huh?
結局それかよ…。
You're going, too, right?
行くだろ お前も？
No, I don't particularly...
いや オレは別に…。
How's Chiriku doing?
地陸は元気にやってるか？
Come to think of it,
ああ そういえば アスマ先生ってば➡
I hear you're acquainted
with Chiriku-san, Asuma-sensei!
地陸さんと知り合いなんだってな。
(アスマ)ああ…。
Yeah...
オレの父さんも カズマって…。
M-My dad's name
was Kazuma and...
You've got some
pretty good moves.
(アスマ)お前さんの筋 悪くない。
Chiriku must've trained
you quite hard.
ずいぶん 地陸に
もまれたんだろう。
No... Chiriku-sama was a great person
at the Fire Temple, you see.
いや… 地陸様は 火ノ寺でも
偉い人だったから 自己流だよ。
It's my own style.
Oh, I see...
So you got that good by yourself.
へぇ そうか。
１人で あそこまで…。
Oh yeah! Hey, Asuma-sensei.
Show him that!
そうだ！ なぁ アスマ先生 コイツにも
あれ 見せてやってくれよ！
That?
あれ？ うむ…。
す… すげえ！
That's incredible...
The trick is to do it
steadily and sharply.
コツは 薄く鋭くだってばよ！
(アスマ)そうだ！
That's right!
Once you learn the trick,
you'll be able to send
そのコツを覚えたら
お前たちのクナイや手裏剣でも➡
your Kunai Knives and Shuriken
right through a tree trunk.
木の幹くらい
貫通させることもできるぞ！
See you around.
じゃあな… がんばれよ！
Good luck.
Hold on!
(ソラ)待ってくれよ！
If you know my father,
I want you to tell me about him.
(ソラ)父さんのこと…
知ってたら 教えてほしい…。
元守護忍十二士の…
カズマって名の！
He was a member of
the Guardian Shinobi Twelve
and his name was Kazuma...
Huh...?
Why was he killed?
なんで 殺されたのか…。
My father didn't do
anything wrong.
父さんは… 間違ったことは
やってない！
That's what I believe...
オレは そう信じて…！
You know him, don't you?!
知ってるよな!?
(アスマ)カズマは…。
Kazuma...
カズマは 信念を貫いて 死んだ。
Kazuma died sticking to
what he believed in.
それが どんな最期であっても…。
No matter how things ended,
he died for the honor
he himself believed in.
ヤツは 自らが信じた
義のために死んだ。
Oh...
じゃ 行くぜ。
Okay, I'm leaving...
H-Hey...
お おい…。
Are you going to do training now?
お前
今から修業しようってのかよ？
クソ…。
うお～！
Damn it...
I won't lose out to you!
お前には 負けねえってばよ！
One, two, three, four...
(フエン)ひい ふう みい よ…
ざっと30ぐらいかしら？
At a glance
it looks like about thirty...
Yeah, around that many...
(フドウ)あぁ そんなものか。
It's going to be quite different
this time around.
(フウカ)
今度は 今までと 訳が違うよ。
We're going to destroy
a village of the Kohaku Clan
火ノ国でも 有数の忍
琥珀一族の村を やるのよ。
with some of the greatest Shinobi
in the Land of Fire.
And...
それも… きっちりと。
With great precision.
We'll kill all of them.
一切を 殺す。
(フドウ)フフ… あぁ。
(フエン)わかってる。
Yeah...
I know. They were just
diversions until now...
前回までは 陽動 今回は…
いよいよ。
This time...
At last...
Oh! Let me know if there are
any Shinobi with the wind property.
(フウカ)あっ 風属性の忍がいたら
教えてね。
That one will be mine.
ソイツは 私がいただくわ。
Hey! Everyone
in the Kohaku Clan!
(フリド)お～い 琥珀一族の諸君！
You're all going to die!
死んじゃうんだぞ！
But your souls
will become sustenance
でも キミらの魂は 未来永劫
火ノ国を守る糧となる！
to protect the Land of Fire
for all eternity!
I promise you that!
オレが 約束する！
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Do it.
やれ。
I look up at the rainbow I saw as a child.
kodomo no koro mita niji wo
But the prism colors are gone,
ima miageru to nanairo de wa naku
Shrouded in mist instead.
yagate kiri ga kakari
I search for you as you change,
jikan wa sugi kawatte yuku
With the passage of time but you're nowhere to be found.
kimi wo sagashite mo doko ni mo inai
I close my eyes and open my heart.
me wo toji kokoro hiraite
And stare hard again just to see if nothing really changes.
mata nagemete mite mo nani mo kawaranai no ka
I need to know.
tashikamete mitai
I make a wish that the mist will clear.
sunao ni narereba kono kiri ga hareru to
If I'm true to myself and shout it out.
kokoro ni negai sou sakenderu
Maybe by losing something.
nanika wo nakushite shimatta koto de sou
There must be something I gain as well.
te ni shita mono mo kitto arun darou
よっしゃ！
勝つわよ！
But we're still confused about adulthood.
dakedo mada bokura wa otona ni tomadoi
はぁ…。
優勝したら 焼き肉一年分！
(ヤマト)違います！
今回は 木ノ葉崩し編からの➡
And searching for the means to live on.
ikito yuku sube sagashiteru
早押しクイズ！
木ノ葉崩しで➡
久しぶりに再結成した
旧いのしかちょうトリオ。
その１人 山中 イノイチの
得意技といえば？
Next Episode
Sora and Naruto, huh?
心乱身の術。
It'd probably be impossible to
quickly hammer formations into them.
(ヤマト)ですが… 奈良 シカクの
木ノ葉秘伝…。
影首縛りの術。
Then Team Kakashi will proceed
with your own training for a while...
(ヤマト)ですが 秋道 チョウザの…。
Then I get to continue the training
I was doing before, right?!
超倍化の術。
No, well, you know,
you need Kakashi-senpai for that...
(ヤマト)ですが… 里で暴れる➡
What? Then what am
I supposed to do?
大蛇をしとめた
自来也様の術は？
Let me see.
そんなの知らねえってばよ。
Why don't you have Asuma
supervise your training?
私たち サスケ君を追いかけてたし…。
Yeah!
オレも 音のヤツらを
足止めしてたからな…。
What? It has to be me?
Next time: "The Two Kings"
The Two Kings
ボク 寝てた。
(ヤマト)タイムアップ！ 正解は
口寄せ 屋台崩しの術でした。
And now it's time for
the Third Leaf Crossing Super Quiz!
"THIRD LEAF CROSSING SUPER QUIZ"
ってことで 全員罰ゲーム！
All right!
(みんな)わぁ～！
I'm going to win.
Will I get a year's supply of barbeque if I win?
No.
Today we'll be playing a buzz-in quiz from
the Destruction of
the Hidden Leaf Village arc!
During the Destruction of
the Hidden Leaf Village,
the previous Ino-Shika-Cho Trio
finally reunite!
Speaking of the specialty technique for
Inoichi Yamanaka, a member of the trio...
Mind Destruction Jutsu!
And!
Shikaku Nara's Secret...
Shadow Strangle Jutsu.
And!
Choza Akimichi's...
Super Expansion Jutsu.
And!
What is Master Jiraiya's Jutsu
that defeated the giant snake
that was rampaging in the village?
I don't know!
We were going after Sasuke then.
And I was held up with the guys from the Sound.
I was sleeping.
Time's up.
The answer is the Summoning:
Bring Down the House Jutsu!
So you all have to
play a penalty game!